We
are not right for each other.
But
Auntie Wen
thinks we are a good match.
They are them,
and I am me.
You...
Hello.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Guan Tiantian.
You must be
Mr. Jiang, in charge of the case.
I'm Bai Qiang's new lawyer.
You want to take over her case?
Yes.
Mr. Jiang,
let's talk.
Nice recording.
Find a media outlet
and get it out there ASAP.
Got it, Mr. Liu.
This time,
I want to see
how you're going to get out of this.
Mr. Lin,
should we contact the PR department?
What's the use of contacting them?
Some people are determined to fight to the death.
They've even resorted to such despicable tactics.
So what do we do now?
Go to the company.
Yes.
They maliciously forged our conversation.
The method is low-level,
but effective.
Now the public opinion is saying that
I can't even tolerate the veterans of the company.
They also said that
I can't compare with my father.
Anger can't solve any problem.
The more angry you are,
the more you need to be calm.
Calm down?
He's clearly trying to block my path to succession.
Then we must not let him succeed.
This recording is fake.
It's a loophole in itself.
We can...
Get out.
I've always said
this woman is a trouble.
This must be Liu Yaping.
Whoever it is,
the result is that
because of her,
the reputation of Lin Group
and the plan to go public
are almost ruined.
Actually,
I just want to use her.
Whether you just play with her
or use her,
if you can't calm the storm,
just marry Liu Yaru as soon as possible.
You know
the relationship network of the Liu family.
Use the background and resources of the Liu family
to stabilize the situation.
Otherwise,
your father and I don't mind changing to
a more obedient heir.
I need to check
which financial reporters
and self-media
have received benefits from Liu Yaping of Lin Group recently.
The key is the people who have contacted the original recording.
Price is not a problem.
I want to know
who made the recording
and
where the original recording is.
Did Ms. Wen leave?
Yeah.
She gave me an ultimatum.
Marry Liu Yaru.
How do you know?
It's not hard to guess.
After all, this is the fastest way
to calm the storm and stabilize the shareholders.
It's in line with her style.
Even if I marry Liu Yaru,
it will only give them
another excuse to attack.
Relying on a woman to consolidate your position?
Then leave the recording to me.
I will find evidence
to prove it's fabricated
and calm this down.
Alright.
I'll get going then.
Are you sure?
Okay.
Send me your contact information.
I'll transfer the money to you right away.
Mr. Wang?
Hello.
My last name is Guan.
I have a technical question.
The reward is not a problem.
A deal is a deal.
Then let the fire
burn more fiercely.
Mr. Lin,
I've traced the recording.
It's from your office's internal system.
The time was
last Thursday afternoon.
The operating account is Chen Fang's.
Chen Fang?
It's impossible.
He has been with me for three years.
The account must have been stolen.
The other party is very careful.
But there is still a loophole in time.
We can start
from all the surveillance footage
and access records during that period.
Alright.
I got it.
And,
regarding the South City land project
managed by Director Liu,
I uncovered many loopholes last time.
The documents are all here.
How to use it
is up to you.
That recording is fake.
You know it.
I know it.
But now it's causing a lot of trouble,
harming the interests of Lin Group,
and the interests of all shareholders,
including you.
I know
this is not what you intended.
You are just
deceived by some people
who are eager to show their ability
but with rough methods.
You mean
I did this?
Immediately withdraw the report and apologize.
Tell the outside world that
it was a malicious retaliation from the fired employee.
We will deal with it internally.
The storm will soon subside.
Lin Group will remain the same.
And you
will still be the respected Chairman Liu.
Lin Jiming,
what are you talking about?
Do you have any evidence
to prove that I did it?
I've noticed
that the South City project
and some projects related to the Liu family
there are some
historical issues
in the land approval process.
To ensure
the compliance of Lin Group's listing,
I must take drastic measures
to immediately cut off
all potential risks.
It's painful,
but necessary.
What are you going to do?
Tell me.
If I
expose these compliance risks now,
immediately terminate the cooperation,
who will be the least able to hold back?
The Liu family
or
those deeply tied to the Liu family's interests.
Who?
Lin Jiming.
How dare you!
Liu Yaping,
I offered you a graceful way out,
but you refused.
Either
you clean up your own mess,
and we all save face,
or
I'll do it for you,
but the consequences
you may not be able to bear.